>> Brian Holt: 欢迎使用 React V5 的完整简介，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Welcome to
the Complete Intro to React V5,
我很想回来再教这个
I am stoked to be back
here teaching this again.
这是我最喜欢的课程
This is my favorite course.
我今天大概会重复大概 17 次，它是先知。
I'll probably repeat that like
17 times today, it's prophetic.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，完成 React的简介，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
the complete Intro to React,
这会让整个人都喜欢写 " React"
this is gonna go over the entirety
of like how to write React.
我们把所有最新的特征都用在钩子上。
And we go over all the latest features,
which is gonna be things like hooks.
这将会是新的有趣的，比如上下文和
And it's gonna be all the new fun that
comes with that such as context and
入口和各种很酷的东西
portals and
all sorts of really cool stuff.
并从这一课程的第四版更新其中的一些内容。
And updating some of those things
from the version four of this course.
而且还会有一些其他的 API 类，比如类和
As well it's gonna be going over some
of the other APIs like classes and
生命周期之类的事情
life cycles and things like that.
这样你就能搞定所有这些东西了
So you get a handle on
all that kind of stuff.
我想让你做的第一件事就是我要你这么做
The first thing I want you to do is,
I want you to head to this bit.ly so
B I T L Y / rect-v5 ，并应在此页面上降落。
B I T L Y /react-v5 and
should land on this page here.
你知道的这些是我的课程笔记
Just so you know,
these are my course notes,
这就是我们要做的事
this is what we're gonna be going over.
所以我在这里还有一个表面，就是我在这里的一切。
So I have another Surface right here,
that's all I have up here.
所以如果你落后了或者你得去约会
So if you fall behind or
you need to come up to date or
任何类似的东西你都能读完
anything like that,
you can just read this as well.
好吗 ?
Okay?
>> Brian Holt: So >> Brian Holt: You
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You
不要把这个课程的前几个版本看在 V5，
do not have to have taken the previous
versions of this course to watch V5,
对这就是第五次的第五次迭代
right this is actually it's V5 in
the sense that it's the fifth iteration.
所以你从零开始，你不用看其他的人来这里。
So you start from zero, you don't have to
watch any of the other ones to get here.
但是，如果您需要讨论 Web 包， V3 实际上仍然有用。
That being said, V3 actually is still
useful if you need to talk about web pack.
如果您需要对路由器进行对话，或者
If you need to talk about react router, or
任何东西， V3 的一切都还是很重要的。
any of those things, everything in
V3 is still very much up to date.
所以，如果你还需要这些东西的话，那就在外面。
So that's out there if you need
some of those things as well.
>> Brian Holt: 这主要是模块化的，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This is meant
to be mostly modular, right?
所以你可以从教训中吸取教训
So that you can kinda skip
from lesson to lesson,
但你要做的就是在它之间移动
but the way that you have to do
that is moving between git commits.
所以如果我去 github.com/BTholt/complete-intro-to-react-
So if I go to
github.com/BTholt/complete-intro-to-react-
-V5 在课程笔记上也有链接
-V5, there's a link to it as
well in the course notes.
>> Brian Holt: Repo。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Repo.
>> Brian Holt: 雷波在这里，就在这里。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: The repo is here,
right there.
所以如果你去了这页然后你向下滚动到它说雷波在这里的地方
So if you go to this page and you scroll
down to where it says the repo is here and
你点击它就会带你到这里来
you click on that it will take you to
here, which is the repo for the course.
在这里，您可以单击落实。
And inside of here,
you can click on the commits.
你可以看到这个项目的所有承诺，对。
And you can see all of the commits for
this project, right.
因此，该课程的每个部分都在一个落实中向前移动。
So each section of this course
moves forward in one commit.
你可以看到你是否点击了其中一个
So you can see if you
click on one of these,
你能看出什么是对的吗
you can see what's been added right?
或者如果你点击其中一个，你可以看到这个被删除或者
Or if you click on one of these,
you can see that this got deleted or
这件事已经更新了
this got updated or something like that.
所以这真的很有助于向你们展示
So this will actually be really helpful
to show you the divs between each part of
当然如果你也要这么做的话
the course if you need to
walk through that as well.
>> Brian Holt: 如果要从其中一个开始，实际上可以
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: If you want to start in the
middle of one of these, you can actually
就说我想从 useState 和 custom hook 开始，就这样。
just say I want to start with useState and
custom hooks and things like that.
这里有个叫 Sourcetree的节目
There's actually a program
out here called Sourcetree,
我就会建议你得到
that I'm going to suggest that you get.
您可以获取 Sourcetreeapp.com。
You can get the Sourcetreeapp.com.
我已经安装好了
I already have it installed.
如果你克隆了雷波和点 Sourcetree 的话
And if you clone the repo and
point Sourcetree to it, no,
我为什么要更新这个
why would I update this.
跳过版本。
Skip version.
开个玩笑而已
[LAUGH] Just kidding.
更新所有内容。
Update all of your things.
但是，你可以在这里看到我在 Sourcetree的这一开放。
But, so you can see here I have
this open here in Sourcetree.
所以如果我想回到这个时代
So if I wanna go back
to this commit in time,
我可以在这里右键单击并说 " 检出" 。
I can actually just say right-click
on here and say Checkout.
会说你确定要这么做吗
It's gonna say,
are you sure you want to do this?
好，首先，这将会消除你所做的任何改变。
Right, so first of all, this will blow
away any changes that you have made.
所以要小心一点对吧
So be be careful of that, right?
但我会说好的
But I'm gonna say okay.
这会让我回到那个承诺的阶段，对吧 ?
And this will actually move me
back to that commit, right?
所以现在我的 repo 将处于那个状态，我可以继续向前，对吗 ?
So now my repo will be in that state,
and I can keep going forward, right?
但如果想再向前走
But if wanna move forward again,
我只能说我想去我们加入 React 路由器的地方
I can just say I wanna go to
where we add React router.
我们也能看到这里的所有潜水夫
We can see all the divs down here as well.
>> Brian Holt: 我可以右键单击并表示检出。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I can just right-click
on this and say checkout.
> > Brian Holt: 现在我就在这里。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And now I will be up here.
最后的最后一个承诺就是你有兴趣
And then ultimately the last commit
in here that's you're interested
这一主题的背景就是这一过程的终结。
in is that theme context
that's the end of this course.
这就像现在的主分支的状态。
So that's like the what the state of
the master branch is in right now.
所有这些分支都是为了中间的反应
All of these other branches are for
intermediate React
你可以在以后再看这个课程
which you can also watch that later
after you're done with this course.
这也很有帮助。
So that's really helpful as well.
>> Brian Holt: 让我们看看。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let's see.
回到这里的页面
Going back to the page here.
你也会看到这些，树枝上的东西。
You'll also see these,
branches things with that.
这些会告诉您在哪里有落实点是正确的。
Those will tell you where
there are commit points right.
但我很快就会
But I'll be very forthcoming and
请指出这是您需要前进的承诺。
calling out this is the commit
that you need to go forward.
我会告诉你你想做什么
I'll tell you which commit
message you wanna go forward to.
>> Brian Holt: Sourcetree 真的很棒。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
Sourcetree is really great.
如果您知道如何在命令行上使用 git ，那么也可以使用该命令。
If you know how to use git on
the commandline, you can also use that.
您还可以使用 GitHub Desktop。
You can also use GitHub Desktop.
我刚给你看了源树
I just showed you Source Tree,
因为我觉得这是最容易开始使用的
because I think that's
the easiest one to start using.
我还建议了 Git 深度
I'd also suggest Git In-depth,
那是我们在 Fronend Masters上的 Nino Zacharenko 的课程
which is a course from
Nino Zacharenko on Frontend Masters.
这是一个非常好的课程你应该把所有需要的东西都教给你
It's a fantastic course that you should
take that'll teach you everything you need
知道 Git的事
to know about Git.
>> Brian Holt: 在处理问题时，这当然会有一些
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Where to file issues,
this course is obviously gonna have some
错误会有拼写错误之类的
mistakes and it's gonna have spelling
errors and things like that.
如果你能打开一个拉力请求
I would,
if you could open a pull request or
文件也会有很大的帮助。
file an issue that would
be super helpful as well.
这前额是我的
This lovely forehead is mine.
我是谁
Who am I?
我叫布莱恩 - 霍尔特
So my name is Brian Holt.
我是微软的高级计划经理
I am a Senior Program Manager
at Microsoft.
我在 Azure 和 Visual Studio 代码的 JavaScript 上工作
I work on JavaScript on Azure and Visual
Studio Code, but for the most part my
作业是使 Azure 成为您要部署 node.js 代码的场所。
job is to make Azure a place that you
want to deploy your node.js code.
我经常在Fron趋向大师赛上我喜欢这里
I'm frequently here in Frontend Masters,
I love it here.
我再也不可能再教任何其他的平台了
I'll never teach on probably
any other platform again.
我很感激他们不断地邀请我回来
And I'm really grateful for
them to keep inviting me back and for
他们所做的一切
everything they do for that.
我有时也在Fron趋向 Happy Hour Happy Hour Happy Hour Happy Hour Happy Hour Happy Happy
I'm also sometimes on Frontend Happy Hour,
which is a podcast where it's descriptive,
我们喝醉了就谈 JavaScript
we get drunk and we talk about JavaScript.
以前我是 LinkedIn的一名工作人员工程师
Previously I was a staff
engineer at LinkedIn,
我是 Netflix 和 Reddit的高级工程师。
I've been a senior engineer at Netflix and
Reddit.
我还在这些小盐湖城的公司工作 Needle 和 KSL
I also worked at these smaller Salt Lake
City based companies Needle and KSL and
新皮肤
New Skin.
我也是 " 诗人 " 的董事会成员
I'm also on the board of Vets Who Code,
我认为这是一个非常棒的组织值得你的时间和捐助
which I think is a fantastic organization
worth your time and donations.
我还和另一个朋友合作
And I also co-founded
with another friend and
莎拉 - 德雷斯纳是一个叫做 Concatenate的会议
master Sarah Dresner
a conference called Concatenate,
这是我们在非洲最大的 JavaScript 会议
which is the biggest JavaScript
conference that we know of in Africa.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Just some more about me.
我住在西雅图和我的妻子和我的狗
I live in Seattle with my wife and my dog.
你会看到整个过程中我绝对爱狗
As you'll see throughout this
course I absolutely love dogs.
我有个小哈瓦那人很可爱
I have a little Havanese and
she's adorable.
我喜欢旅行
And I love to travel.
我已经到过 40 或 50 个国家了
I've been to 40 or
50 countries at this point.
我去年有 97 个航班
I took 97 flights last year.
这是一个有趣的事实。
That's an interesting fact.
用了近 30 万英里的流感。
Took the flu almost 300,000 miles.
我再也不会那样做了
I will never do that again.
请在 Twitter， Instagram， GitHub和 LinkedIn上赶上我。
And please catch up with me on Twitter,
Instagram, GitHub, LinkedIn.
如果您将我添加到 LinkedIn ，我一定会将您添加回来。
If you add me to LinkedIn I'll
definitely add you back.
别担心
So no worries there.
为什么会创建此课程 ?
Why was this course created?
我只想在这里向 Fronto Masters的船员大喊大叫
I just want to give a huge shout to
the crew here at Frontend Masters.
他们很想和你一起工作
They've been amazing to work with, and
我最喜欢的事情之一就是这个课程实际上是开源的。
one of my favorite things about that is
that this course is actually open source.
所以这个你在看的这个网站，请大家分享。
So this website that you're looking at
here, please share it with everyone.
我喜欢他们让我来做这些课程
I love that they allow me to come in and
do these courses and
有这些训练并付钱让我去做
have these trainings and pay me to do it.
同时呢，
And at the same time,
让我打开源头让所有人都能得到
allow me to open source these so
that they're available to everyone.
我觉得视频很棒
I think the videos are great.
这就是为什么我花了很多时间
That's why I put a lot
of time into these and
所以我觉得我们可以为他们负责
that's why I think we can charge for them.
但我认为这种知识应该自由地分享。
But I think that that knowledge
should be freely shared.
我很感谢 Fronend Masters 鼓励我这么做
And I'm really grateful that
Frontend Masters encourages me to do these
都是些什么
kind of things.
最后一件事，如果你想在 GitHub 上启动 repo ，那就好了。
And last thing here, if you wanna start
the repo on GitHub that would be great.
这就是我的自我，那就是重要的部分， [ LAUGH] 只是开玩笑的。
It strokes my ego and that's
the important part, [LAUGH] just kidding.
它确实有助于它得到更远的地方，这也是一件好事。
It does help it get farther reach
which is always a good thing as well.
>> Brian Holt: 是的，我们会开始学习一些 React。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And with that, yeah, we'll
start getting into learning some React.